罗斯  莫妮卡
Ross, Mon.
我可以带人去参加你爸妈的结婚周年派对吗
Is it okay if I bring someone to your parents' anniversary party?
没问题  好啊
Sure.  Yeah.
你要带谁去
Who's the guy?
他叫派克  我们在洗衣店里认识的
His name is Parker, and I met him at the cleaners.
他在你外套里放了点浆糊吗
Did he put a little starch in your bloomers?
那是谁说的
Who said that?
不是  但他人真的很棒
No, he's really great, though.
他对生命异常热忱
He has this incredible zest for life.
他把我当女王一样对待
He treats me like a queen.
不过他晚上在床上会把我当作淘气少女
Except at night when he treats me like the naughty girl I am.
对了  今年由我来向爸妈致辞
By the way, would it be okay if I give the toast
可以吗
to mom and dad this year?
经历过20周年纪念日的意外后  你还是想吗
Yeah, you sure you want to after what happened at their 20th?
我真的很想
Yeah. I'd really like to.
希望这次妈不会嘘你
Okay, hopefully this time Mom won't boo you.
太好了  每年都是罗斯致词
Yes! Every year Ross makes the toast,
他的话总能把大家感动得痛哭流涕
and it's always really moving, and always makes them cry.
今年  我要把他们弄哭
This year, I'm gonna make them cry.
你还不知道他们为什么最爱罗斯吗
You wonder why Ross is their favorite?
不是  只要罗斯一致词
No, really. Any time Ross makes a toast,
大家都会哭着拥抱他  拍他的背
everyone cries and hugs him and pats him on the back.
他们都会走过来跟我说"天啊  你哥哥"
And they all come up to me and say, "God, your brother."
你知道今天他们今年会怎么说吗
You know what they're gonna say this year?
"天啊  你"
"God, you."
我向你保证至少有一个人会哭
Well, I can promise you, at least one person will be crying.
我是演员  每个称职的演员都是想哭就哭
I'm an actor, and any actor worth his salt can cry on cue.
真的吗  你做得到吗
Really? You can do that?
开什么玩笑  看着
Oh, you kidding me? Watch.
你们都盯着我看  我哭不出来
Well, I can't do it with you guys watching me!
《老友记》  第八季  第18集  盖勒夫妇的结婚纪念日
Friends S08E18 The One In Massapequa
你在做什么  我在写我的演讲稿
What are you doing?  I'm working on my toast for the party.
我称之为"2002年最佳催泪弹"
Or as I like to call it: "Sobfest 2002."
你看  是只小狗
Hey, check this out.  It's a dog.
是只死狗
It's a dead dog.
这是琪琪  在我高中时死掉了
That's ChiChi. She died when I was in high school.
你要在父母的结婚纪念日上
It's your parents' anniversary
谈一只死狗吗
and you're going to talk about their dead pet?
这个素材不错吧
It's good stuff, huh?
乔伊  你准备好要送我爸妈的礼物了吗
Joey? You got a present for my parents? That's so sweet.
是啊  为了纪念他们结婚35周年
Yeah. In honor of their 35th wedding anniversary,
我用他们的名字为一颗星星命名
I had a star named after them.
那简直太酷了
That is so cool.
我还给他们买了老年人的性爱宝典
And I got them a book on Kama Sutra for the Elderly.
你们有多余的缎带吗
Do you guys have any extra ribbon?
当然有  你要什么样的
Yeah. Sure. What do you need?
我们有蕾丝  缎子  棉缎
We got lace, satin, sateen,
酒椰纤维  条纹布  毛毡
raffia, gingham, felt...
我想我的蛋蛋应该也放在这里了
And I think my testicles may be in here too.
琪琪  我爱死这只狗了
ChiChi! Oh, I loved this dog.
莫妮卡没装牙套是因为琪琪得动膝盖手术
Monica couldn't get braces because ChiChi needed knee surgery.
什么
What?
就是你这个两百磅的大胖子骑着它到处跑的
You're the 200pounder 11yearold who rode her!
大伙们  他是派克  派克  这是...
Hey! Everybody, this is Parker. Parker, this is...
不  别告诉我
No, don't tell me.
让我猜  乔伊  莫妮卡  罗斯  瑞秋
Let me guess: Joey, Monica, Ross, Rachel...
对不起  菲比没有提过你
...and I'm sorry, Phoebe didn't mention you.
钱德勒  我开玩笑呢  你已经是我的最爱了
Chandler, I'm kidding! Already you're my favorite.
跟我谈谈你们自己的事吧
Why don't all of you tell me a little about your self?
事实上我们该走了
Actually, I'm sorry. We probably should get going.
典型的罗斯作风
Classic Ross!
瑞秋  你好漂亮  我可以吗
Rachel, look how you glow! May I ?
我想你已经不请自来了
I think you already are.
瑞秋  你体内孕育着一个小生命
Rachel, you have life growing inside you.
这世上还有什么更神奇...
Is there anything in this world more miraculous...
一张狗狗照片  这是谁的狗
A picture of a dog! Whose is this?
那是我家以前养的狗  它已经死了
That's my old dog. He passed away years ago.
至少你很幸运能拥有它
Well, at least you were lucky to have him.
汪汪  我的老朋友  汪汪
Bowwow, old friend. Bowwow.
派对在哪里举行
So where's the party?
在岛上的马沙皮卡
It's out on the island. It's in Massapequa.
马沙皮卡  听起来像个神奇的地方
Massapequa, it sounds like a magical place.
跟我介绍一下吧
Tell me about Massapequa,
它是美国原住民历史上的名胜吗
is it steeped in Native American history?
那里有原住民帐篷形状的艾比餐厅
Well, there is an Arby's in the shape of a tepee.
我拿了题词卡
I've got my note cards.
你拿礼物了吗  拿了
You got the presents?  Yeah.
我拿车钥匙了  我们要开车吗
And I've got the car keys.  We're driving?
对  太棒了
Yeah.  Aces.
他似乎是个好人  对  我很喜欢他
So he seems like a nice guy.  Yeah, I like him a lot.
你想拖延一会去搭计程车吗
You want to hang back and take our own cab?
当然  不然我就不去了
Okay, otherwise I'm not going.
妈  这个派对简直太棒了
Hey, Mom.  This is such a great party!
三十五年  令人佩服
Thirtyfive years. Very impressive.
你们有什么婚姻的至理名言吗
Do you have any pearls of wisdom?
杰克  食物上为什么要插这么尖的牙签
Jack?  Why would you serve food on such a sharp stick?
这个问题不错  爸爸  这个问题不错
It's a good question, Dad. It's a good question.
恭喜你们  谢谢  我们很兴奋
Congratulations, you two.  Thank you, we're so excited.
还要恭喜你们结婚了
And also, congratulations on your wedding.
我们能跟你们谈一下吗  好吧
Can we talk to you for just a moment?  Yeah.
这只是件小事
It's just a little thing.
我们觉得你们未婚生子
While we think it's simply marvelous
完全没有问题
that you're having this baby out of wedlock...
但我们有些朋友思想没有那么开放
some of our friends are less openminded.
所以我们告诉他们你们结婚了  什么
Which is why we told them you're married.  What?
谢谢你们愿意配合
Thanks for going along with this.
爸  我们得假装我们结婚了吗
Dad, we have to pretend that we're married?
儿子  我为了今晚专门剃了耳毛
Son, I had to shave my ears for tonight.
这件事你也能做到
You can do this.
你能相信吗  就是啊
Can you believe that?  I know.
既然剃了耳毛  就不能连鼻毛一起处理一下吗
If you do the ears, you may as well take a pass at the nosal area.
我不想撒谎说我们结婚了
No, no. I don't want to have to lie about us being married.
我也不想
No, I know. I don't either.
但这是他们的派对  而且仅此一晚而己
But you know what ? It's their party, and it's one night.
我们不必说谎  我们只要不说话就行
We don't have to lie. We just won't say anything.
如果有人提起  我们只要微笑点头
If it comes up again, we'll just smile, we'll nod along...
罗斯  瑞秋
Ross?  Rachel?
嗨  丽莎阿姨  丹叔叔
Hi, Aunt Lisa. Uncle Dan.
恭喜你们怀孕  还结了婚
Congratulations on the baby and on the wedding.
这算是送你们的新婚礼物
Here's a little something to get you started.
你们的婚后生活过得如何
So how's married life treating you?
不可思议  太棒了  我们可喜欢结婚了
Unbelievable. It's great!  We love marriage.
待会见
We'll see you later.
好漂亮的地方  好棒的夜晚
What a beautiful place. What a great night.
我得告诉你们
I have to tell you,
能跟你们一起待在C宴会厅
being here with all of you in Event Room C...
我觉得好幸运  想想这里曾有过的美好时光
...I feel so lucky. Think of the good times that happened here.
生日  毕业舞会  犹太教成人礼
The birthdays, the proms, the mitzvahs, both bar and bat!
但任凭什么都比不上今晚
But none of them will compare with tonight!
天啊  我想铭记这个瞬间
My God, I don't want to forget this moment!
我要在脑海中帮你们拍张照
It's like I want to take a mental picture of you all.
咔嚓
Click.
我觉得闪光灯没开
I don't think the flash went off.
我要去趟洗手间  马上回来
I'm gonna find the men's room. I'll be right back.
我跟你一起去  快来
I'll go with you.  Come on, come on.
有人躲在某个地方端着麻醉枪
Somewhere there is someone with a tranquilizer gun...
握着大蝴蝶网  在找那个家伙
...and a huge butterfly net looking for that man.
我也想上厕所
I have to go to the bathroom too,
但我不想让他夸奖我的小弟弟
but I don't want him complimenting my thing.
还好我们没在车上  他有安静的时候吗
So glad we weren't in the car. Did he ever let up?
他称长岛高速公路为"水泥奇迹"
He called the Long Island Expressway a "concrete miracle."
这个房间  这个夜晚
This room. This night.
那个服务生  他的鞋子
That waiter! His shoes!
我要在脑海中拍张照
I must take a mental picture!
抱歉
Sorry.
你们在取笑派克吗
Were you guys making fun of Parker?
那得看你听到了多少
That depends, how much did you hear?
他是有点狂热  可那有什么不对
He's a little enthusiastic. What's wrong with that?
他太过火了  那又怎么样  我喜欢他
It's so much.  Well, so what? I like him.
我会取笑你们的约会对象吗
Do I make fun of the people you've dated?
泰格  珍妮丝  蒙娜
Tag, Janice, Mona.
不  因为朋友不会那么做
No, because friends don't do that.
你们想知道我的想法吗
But do you want my opinion?
依我看来
Do you want it? 'Cause in my opinion,
你们的约会纪录加起来
your collective dating record
基本等同于人渣史
reads like a who's who of human crap!
我觉得好内疚  我知道
I feel terrible.  I know.
蒙娜有哪里不好
What was wrong with Mona?
快打开  好耶  宝贝
Open it, open it, open it.  Yeah, baby!
我们都没听说你们举办了婚礼
So we never got to hear about your wedding.
我们很讶异自己没有受到邀请
We were surprised we weren't invited.
不  只有我们父母和几位亲友参加
No, no, it was just our parents and 1 or 2 friends.
婚礼的规模很小
It was a small wedding.
但场面很美
But it was beautiful.
婚礼虽小  一应俱全
It was small, but kind of spectacular.
你们在哪里举行的婚礼
Where did you have it?
在巴巴多斯悬崖上的黄昏婚礼
On a cliff in Barbados, at sunset.
我走上红毯时  史提夫·汪达唱着《她真美》
And Stevie Wonder sang "Isn't She Lovely" as I walked down the aisle.
真的吗  史提夫是我们家的朋友
Really?  Yeah. Stevie's a family friend.
天啊  那真的是太棒了
Oh, my God. That sounds amazing.
我想看照片  对  我也是
I'd love to see pictures.  Yeah, so would I.
你们不会相信安妮·莱波维兹
You wouldn't think Annie Liebowitz
会忘了装底片
would forget to put film in the camera.
请允许我们失陪一下
Would you excuse us for a second?
你这是要干什么
What are you doing?
怎么了  我又不是你
What? I'm not you.
那可能是我唯一一场婚礼
This may be my only wedding I ever have.
我希望婚礼很精彩  好吧
And I want it to be amazing.  Okay.
或许我该骑着哈雷摩托入场
Maybe I rode in on a Harley.
罗斯  我们得编得现实一点
Okay. Ross, it has to be realistic.
你还好吗  你一直不太讲话
Say, are you okay? You seem kind of quiet.
我没事  我很好  我跟你在一起
No, I'm fine. I'm great. I'm with you.
而我跟你在一起  活着真好
And I'm with you. What a great time to be alive!
看看这个送盘器
Look at this plate bouncy thing.
这是个天才发明  解决了盘子分发的问题
What an inspired solution to man's platedispensing problems.
生蚝  让我来喂你  你不必那么做
Oysters! Let me feed you one.  That's not necessary.
拜托  我不吃...
Please?  Actually I don't eat...
你不吃的话我绝不罢休  好吧
I won't quit until you try one.  Okay, fine, fine.
很棒
Good.
是什么味道  我从来没吃过
What're they like? I've never had one.
那就尝尝看  看起来太奇怪了
Why don't you just try one.  No, they look too weird.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
准备致辞
Just going over my toast.
他们俩绝对想不到我会说什么
Those two will never know what hit them.
我等不及了  他们会痛哭流涕
I can't wait. They'll cry so hard,
以至于喘不过气来
they'll be fighting for breath.
如果你需要的话  我可以按住他们  让你
If you want to, I could just hold them down and you could just...
我戴着蕾丝婚纱  由比利时盲人修女织成
And my veil was lace, made by blind Belgian nuns.
盲人
Blind?
她们本来没瞎  但这份工作非常伤眼力
Not at first, but it's very intricate work.
她们说虽然眼睛瞎了  但还是很值得的
They said even though they lost their sight, it's all worth it.
我敢说你看起来很漂亮  我不知道
I bet you looked beautiful.  Well, I don't know about that.
但有些宾客说
But there were some people that said
我看起来像漂浮的天使
I looked like a floating angel.
你是怎么求的婚
How did you propose?
对  那个故事很精彩
Oh, yeah, that's a great story.
事实上  我带她去了天文馆
Well, actually, I took her to the planetarium.
那是我们第一次约会的地方
That's where we had our first date.
她走进来
She walked in
我在房间里铺满了她最喜欢的百合花
and I had the room filled with lilies, her favorite flower.
简直太浪漫了  我还想听完呢
That is so sweet!  I want to hear the rest!
音响系统里传出弗莱德·艾斯塔的歌声
Then Fred Astaire singing, "The Way You Look Tonight"
《你今晚的样子》  此时灯光熄灭
came on the sound system, and the lights came down,
我单脚跪地
I got on one knee...
圆顶从左至右用星星拼成一行字
and written across the dome, in the stars, were the words:
"你愿意嫁给我吗 "
"Will you marry me?"
戒指有我的拳头那么大
And the ring was the size of my fist.
菲比  听着
Hey, Phoebe? Look...
我要对你道歉  我们太不厚道了
...I want to apologize about before. Okay? We were being jerks.
派克人很好  我想多了解他
Parker's a nice guy, and I'd like to get to know him.
那你最好快去找他
Then you better do it now.
为什么  因为我要杀了他
Why?  Because I'm gonna kill him.
什么  你们说得没错
What? What?  You guys were right.
他对所有事都太热衷了
He's too excited about everything.
我也很喜欢生命
I'm all for living life,
但这是盖勒夫妇结婚35周年派对
but this is the Gellers' 35th anniversary.
我们摸着良心说话  这个派对烂透了
Let's call a spade a spade. This party stinks.
就是  我简直无聊到了极点
I know. I'm having the worst time.
那边取自助餐要排15分钟的队
There was a 15minute line for the buffet,
等我好不容易拿到盘子
and when I got to the plates...
结果踩到一大坨鼻涕滑倒了
...I slipped on a giant booger.
你确定那不是生蚝吗
Are you sure it wasn't an oyster?
有可能  我没看
It could've been. I didn't look at it.
我把它抹在钱德勒的外套上  拔腿就溜
I just wiped it on Chandler's coat and got the hell out.
我还以为他是个好人  我对他真的很期待
I thought he was a great guy. I was so excited about him.
嘿  你应该对他充满期待
Well, hey, you should be excited about him.
他没有什么不对  他是个好人
There's nothing wrong with him. He's a good guy.
真的吗  对  你知道吗
You think?  Yeah, you know what I think?
我们都太悲观了  你说得对
I think we were all just being too negative.  You're right.
他只是在拥抱生命而已
You're right. He's just embracing life.
我们都应该向派克学习
We could all stand to be a little more like Parker.
你知道吗  我就跟他一样
You know what? I'm like him!
我是个积极乐观的人
I'm a sunny, positive person!
事实上  你现在稍微有点激动了
Actually, you have a little bit of an edge.
你小子说什么
What's that now?
是派克  看  兔子舞
Oh, it's Parker!  Look, the Bunny Hop!
我喜欢  是吗
Oh, I love it!  You do?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
跟着音乐学动物跳舞  来吧
People acting like animals to music? Come on!
好吧  该致词了
Okay, it's time for the toast.
我知道往年一向都是由罗斯来致词
I know that normally Ross gives the toast,
但今年由我来
but this year I'm gonna do it.
别这样  内容会很精彩
No, it's gonna be great. Really.
好的
Okay.
妈  爸  我结婚时
Mom, Dad, when I got married...
令我对婚姻充满信心的原因之一
...one of the things that made me sure that I could do it
就是你们这对模范夫妻为我做出的表率
was the amazing example the two of you set for me.
为了那一点及其他种种  我要感谢你们
For that, and for so many other things, I want to thank you.
这句话我或许不常说  但...
I know I probably don't say it enough, but...
我爱你们
I love you.
我环顾四周
When I look around this room,
想起那些无法出席的人  便心生悲伤
I'm saddened by the thought of those who could not be with us.
我亲爱的外婆
Nana, my beloved grandmother,
她肯定很想来
who would so want to be here.
但她来不了...
But she can't...
因为她死了
...because she's dead.
我们的狗琪琪也是一样
As is our dog, ChiChi.
你们看它多可爱... 那是以前的事了
I mean, look how cute she is... was.
帮我个忙  请把这个传给我爸妈
Do me a favor, pass this to my parents.
记住它死了  好吗  它和奶奶都不在了
Remember she's dead, okay? Her and Nana, gone.
还有谁记得...
Does anybody remember when...
黛博拉·威格在《亲蜜关系》中
...Debra Winger had to say goodbye
不得不跟她的孩子们说再见的样子
to her children in Terms of Endearment?
你们没看过吗
Didn't see that?
没有人爱看电影吗
No movie fans?!
你们想听些悲伤的故事吗
You want to hear something sad?
有一天我在《60分钟》
The other day, I was watching 60 Minutes
看到罗马尼亚孤儿院的报导
and there was this piece on orphans in Romania...
他们遭到抛弃  无法再爱
...who have been so neglected that they were incapable of love.
你们都是铁血心肠
You people are made of stone!
敬爸妈  随便啦
Here's to Mom and Dad. Whatever!
谢谢莫妮卡  那段致辞很有意思
Thank you, Monica. That was interesting.
很有意思吧  杰克
Wasn't it interesting, Jack?
为什么我不记得这只狗了
Why don't I remember this dog?
罗斯  你为什么不为我们致词呢
Ross? Why don't you give us your toast now?
不  妈  今年只有莫妮卡致辞
Oh, no, Mom. It's just Monica this year.
在我们35周年的派对上
You're not saying anything?
你都不打算不致词吗
On our 35th wedding anniversary?
当然不是
No, of course.
各位
Everybody?
我只想说
I just wanted to say...
代表我的新婚妻子瑞秋...
...on behalf of my new bride, Rachel...
还有我自己
...and myself, that if...
如果我们结婚35年后
...if in 35 years,
有你们一半幸福...
we're half as happy as you guys are...
我们会觉得自己是全世界最幸运的人
...we'll count ourselves the luckiest people in the world.
罗斯
Oh, Ross.
希望外婆还活着听到罗斯的致词
I just wish Nana were alive to hear Ross' toast.
天啊  这个走廊的灯光真漂亮
My God, what a fantastically welllit hallway.
你要喝点东西吗   譬如水跟镇静剂
Can I get you something to drink, like a water and Valium?
我得说这间公寓...
I must say, this apartment, it's...
我不知道该怎么形容
there are no words.
谢天谢地  宛如天堂
Thank God.  It's a haven.
位于三楼的天堂  现代伊甸国
A thirdfloor paradise, a modern Eden in the midst.
我知道  我了解
Yeah, I know, I know. Gotcha.
听着  我们坐下来放松一下吧
Listen, why don't we just sit and relax,
安静地彼此依偎
just be with each other quietly.
听起来不错
That sounds great.
天啊  这是我这辈子坐过
My god. This is the most comfortable couch
最舒服的沙发
I've ever sat on in my entire life.
我们试点别的  我们玩个游戏吧
Let's try something else. Let's play a game.
我喜欢玩游戏  不是吧
I love games.  Shocking.
我们来玩...
Let's play the game of...
谁能最久不说话的游戏
...who can stay quiet the longest.
或是玩层层叠
Or Jenga.
我们先玩沉默游戏  记住
Let's play this one first, and remember,
先说话的人就输了
whoever talks first loses.
我输了  现在来玩层层叠  我的天啊
I lose, now Jenga.  Oh, my God.
哪里不对劲吗
Is something wrong?
你还知道什么是"不对劲"吗
Wrong? You know the word "wrong"?
难道一切不是美好又神奇吗
Everything isn't perfect? Everything isn't magical?
难道一切不是闪耀又璀璨吗
Everything isn't aglow with the light of a million fairies?
那只是刹车灯而已  派克
They were just brake lights, Parker!
对不起我把塞车形容得如此美好
Excuse me for putting a good spin on a traffic jam.
你不必对所有事物都做美化
You don't have to put a good spin on everything!
抱歉  我就是这样一个乐观的人
I'm sorry. That's who I am. I'm a positive person.
不  我才是个乐观的人
No, I'm a positive person.
你像是吃了抗忧郁药的圣诞老人
You are like Santa Claus on Prozac.
在迪士尼乐园享受性爱
At Disneyland, getting laid!
那你想要我怎样  更悲观一些吗
So what do you want me to do? You want me to be more negative?
压抑心中的快乐吗
You want me to be less happy?
使劲压抑
Much less happy.
好吧  那引用罗斯的话"我最好走了"
Fine. Well, then to quote Ross, "I better be going."
再见
So long!
你出去的时候  别让"全世界最棒的门"
Don't let the "best door in the world"
打到屁股了
hit you in the ass on your way out.
这是你一辈子吵过最不可思议的一架吧
Isn't this the most incredible fight you've had in your entire life?
你坐在边车里
And then we could've gone from the ceremony
我们从婚礼现场走到婚宴厅
to the reception with you in the sidecar.
那样行不通啊
Ross, it just wouldn't be feasible.
鸽子叼着戒指戴到你手上
But a dove placing the ring on your finger
就没有问题
would've been no problem.
今晚跟你结婚感觉太棒了
It was fun being married to you tonight.
对  这四百块真好赚
Yeah, and it was the easiest 400 bucks I've ever made.
罗斯  我能问你一件事吗  好吧
Okay, Ross, can I ask you something?  Yeah.
在天文馆求婚
That proposal at the planetarium?
我知道  那太蠢了
I know, I know. It was stupid.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
有百合花  那首歌  还有星星
With the lilies, and the song and the stars?
简直妙不可言
It was really wonderful.
你是随便编的吗
Did you just make that up?
我们交往时  我想过要那么做
I thought of it when we were going out.
那就是我想象中跟你求婚的样子
That's how I imagined I would ask you to marry me.
要拒绝你一定很难
Well, that would've been very hard to say no to.
还好我没有那么做
It's a good thing I didn't do it,
因为听起来那会是个昂贵的婚礼
because it sounds like it would have been a very expensive wedding.
好吧  晚安  晚安
Okay, good night.  Good night.
如果边车有挡风玻璃
Even if the sidecar had a windscreen
你的头发不会被吹乱呢
so your hair wouldn't get messed up?
我会考虑的  我已经满足了
I will think about it.  That's all I'm asking.
好吧  够了  我放弃
Okay, that's it. I give up.
在爸妈的40周年派对上
At Mom and Dad's 40th anniversary,
由你来致词
you're the one giving the speech.
我不明白他们为什么没哭
You know, I don't understand why they didn't cry.
你的致词很感人
It was a beautiful speech.
得了吧  你提到有关真爱的事情
Come on.  All that stuff you said about true love?
你说得对  我们从爸妈身上学到了很多
You were right. We did learn a lot from Mom and Dad.
琪琪在照片上调皮地笑着
That picture of ChiChi with her mischievous grin.
还有外婆那一段
And what you said about Nana?
她真的会很想去参加
Yeah, she really would've wanted to be there.
你知道吗
And you know what?
我想她真的去了
I think she was.
天啊  罗斯  你是怎么办到的
Oh, good God, Ross, how the hell do you do it?